[
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"But in all things approving ourselves as the ministers of God, in much patience.\"",
        "type": "in afflictions, in necessities, in distresses",
        "reference": "2C 6:4",
        "answer": "in afflictions, in necessities, in distresses"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:15, which two's concord is questioned?",
        "type": "Christ (with) Belial",
        "reference": "2C 6:15",
        "answer": "Christ (with) Belial"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Knowing therefore the terror of the Lord, we persuade men.\"",
        "type": "but we are made manifest unto God; and I trust also are made manifest in your consciences",
        "reference": "2C 5:11",
        "answer": "but we are made manifest unto God; and I trust also are made manifest in your consciences"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:16, what are ye?",
        "type": "the temple of the living God",
        "reference": "2C 6:16",
        "answer": "the temple of the living God"
    },
    {
        "question": "How are we desiring to be clothed upon with our house which is from heaven in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "earnestly",
        "reference": "2C 5:2",
        "answer": "earnestly"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whom do we persuade in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "men",
        "reference": "2C 5:11",
        "answer": "men"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:17, what will the Lord do?",
        "type": "I will receive you",
        "reference": "2C 6:17",
        "answer": "I will receive you"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:8, from what are we willing to be absent?",
        "type": "the body",
        "reference": "2C 5:8",
        "answer": "the body"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:15, how should they live?",
        "type": "(not live unto themselves, but) unto him which died for them, and rose again",
        "reference": "2C 5:15",
        "answer": "(not live unto themselves, but) unto him which died for them, and rose again"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:21, why hath God made him to be sin for us?",
        "type": "that we might be made the righteousness of God in him",
        "reference": "2C 5:21",
        "answer": "that we might be made the righteousness of God in him"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:21, what hath God made him to be for us?",
        "type": "sin",
        "reference": "2C 5:21",
        "answer": "sin"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:1, what receive you not in vain?",
        "type": "the grace of God",
        "reference": "2C 6:1",
        "answer": "the grace of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:16, who will dwell in them?",
        "type": "(I) God",
        "reference": "2C 6:16",
        "answer": "(I) God"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is unfeigned in 2 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "love",
        "reference": "2C 6:6",
        "answer": "love"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:5, who hath wrought us for the selfsame thing?",
        "type": "(he) God",
        "reference": "2C 5:5",
        "answer": "(he) God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: We then, as workers together with him, beseech you also that ye receive not the grace of God in vain.",
        "type": "2 Corinthians 6:1",
        "reference": "2C 6:1",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 6:1"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:7, by what do we walk?",
        "type": "by faith",
        "reference": "2C 5:7",
        "answer": "by faith"
    },
    {
        "question": "What constraineth us in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "the love of Christ",
        "reference": "2C 5:14",
        "answer": "the love of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: (For we walk by faith, not by sight:)",
        "type": "2 Corinthians 5:7",
        "reference": "2C 5:7",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 5:7"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:2, when have I heard thee?",
        "type": "in a time accepted",
        "reference": "2C 6:2",
        "answer": "in a time accepted"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:13, what be ye also?",
        "type": "enlarged",
        "reference": "2C 6:13",
        "answer": "enlarged"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:14, what do we thus judge?",
        "type": "that if one died for all, then were all dead",
        "reference": "2C 5:14",
        "answer": "that if one died for all, then were all dead"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 5:8.",
        "type": "We are confident, I say, and willing rather to be absent from the body, and to be present with the Lord.",
        "reference": "2C 5:8",
        "answer": "We are confident, I say, and willing rather to be absent from the body, and to be present with the Lord."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:6, when are we confident?",
        "type": "always",
        "reference": "2C 5:6",
        "answer": "always"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is a new creature in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "(he) if any man be in Christ",
        "reference": "2C 5:17",
        "answer": "(he) if any man be in Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 6 which uses the word: blamed",
        "type": "Giving no offence in any thing, that the ministry be not blamed:",
        "reference": "2C 6:3",
        "answer": "Giving no offence in any thing, that the ministry be not blamed:"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"For we know that if our earthly house of this tabernacle were dissolved.\"",
        "type": "we have a building of God, an house not made with hands, eternal in the heavens",
        "reference": "2C 5:1",
        "answer": "we have a building of God, an house not made with hands, eternal in the heavens"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:17, where come?",
        "type": "out from among them",
        "reference": "2C 6:17",
        "answer": "out from among them"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are passed away in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "old things",
        "reference": "2C 5:17",
        "answer": "old things"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is eternal in the heavens in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "(we have) a building of God (an house not made with hands)",
        "reference": "2C 5:1",
        "answer": "(we have) a building of God (an house not made with hands)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:7, what is on the right hand and on the left?",
        "type": "the armour of righteousness",
        "reference": "2C 6:7",
        "answer": "the armour of righteousness"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:16, what shall they be?",
        "type": "my (God's) people",
        "reference": "2C 6:16",
        "answer": "my (God's) people"
    },
    {
        "question": "What hath no agreement with idols in 2 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "the temple of God",
        "reference": "2C 6:16",
        "answer": "the temple of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:14, which two's communion is questioned?",
        "type": "light (with) darkness",
        "reference": "2C 6:14",
        "answer": "light (with) darkness"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was God reconciling unto himself in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "the world",
        "reference": "2C 5:19",
        "answer": "the world"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:1, how is the building of God not made?",
        "type": "with hands",
        "reference": "2C 5:1",
        "answer": "with hands"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:3, where give no offence?",
        "type": "in any thing",
        "reference": "2C 6:3",
        "answer": "in any thing"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:2, when is the accepted time?",
        "type": "now",
        "reference": "2C 6:2",
        "answer": "now"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:19, what hath God committed unto us?",
        "type": "the word of reconciliation",
        "reference": "2C 5:19",
        "answer": "the word of reconciliation"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:18, what shall ye be?",
        "type": "my (the Lord's) sons and daughters",
        "reference": "2C 6:18",
        "answer": "my (the Lord's) sons and daughters"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: For the love of Christ constraineth us; because we thus judge, that if one died for all, then were all dead:",
        "type": "2 Corinthians 5:14",
        "reference": "2C 5:14",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 5:14"
    },
    {
        "question": "What be not blamed in 2 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "the ministry",
        "reference": "2C 6:3",
        "answer": "the ministry"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 6:15.",
        "type": "And what concord hath Christ with Belial? or what part hath he that believeth with an infidel?",
        "reference": "2C 6:15",
        "answer": "And what concord hath Christ with Belial? or what part hath he that believeth with an infidel?"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:16, how know we no man henceforth?",
        "type": "after the flesh",
        "reference": "2C 5:16",
        "answer": "after the flesh"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:3, how shall we not be found?",
        "type": "naked",
        "reference": "2C 5:3",
        "answer": "naked"
    },
    {
        "question": "Before which seat must we appear in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "the judgment seat of Christ",
        "reference": "2C 5:10",
        "answer": "the judgment seat of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Wherefore come out from among them, and be ye separate, saith the Lord, and touch not the unclean thing; and I will receive you,",
        "type": "2 Corinthians 6:17",
        "reference": "2C 6:17",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 6:17"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 6:2.",
        "type": "(For he saith, I have heard thee in a time accepted, and in the day of salvation have I succoured thee: behold, now is the accepted time; behold, now is the day of salvation.)",
        "reference": "2C 6:2",
        "answer": "(For he saith, I have heard thee in a time accepted, and in the day of salvation have I succoured thee: behold, now is the accepted time; behold, now is the day of salvation.)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:9, what may we be?",
        "type": "accepted of him (the Lord)",
        "reference": "2C 5:9",
        "answer": "accepted of him (the Lord)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:11, what are we knowing?",
        "type": "the terror of the Lord",
        "reference": "2C 5:11",
        "answer": "the terror of the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:8, with whom are we willing to be present?",
        "type": "with the Lord",
        "reference": "2C 5:8",
        "answer": "with the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:13, how do I speak?",
        "type": "as unto my children",
        "reference": "2C 6:13",
        "answer": "as unto my children"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:13, what is to God?",
        "type": "(it) whether we be beside ourselves",
        "reference": "2C 5:13",
        "answer": "(it) whether we be beside ourselves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"For he hath made him to be sin for us, who knew.\"",
        "type": "no sin; that we might be made the righteousness of God in him",
        "reference": "2C 5:21",
        "answer": "no sin; that we might be made the righteousness of God in him"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:4, who groan?",
        "type": "we that are in this tabernacle",
        "reference": "2C 5:4",
        "answer": "we that are in this tabernacle"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:10, when are we rejoicing?",
        "type": "alway",
        "reference": "2C 6:10",
        "answer": "alway"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:1, as what together with him do we beseech you?",
        "type": "workers",
        "reference": "2C 6:1",
        "answer": "workers"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:2, what is from heaven?",
        "type": "our house",
        "reference": "2C 5:2",
        "answer": "our house"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:18, what hath God given to us?",
        "type": "the ministry of reconciliation",
        "reference": "2C 5:18",
        "answer": "the ministry of reconciliation"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:15, for whom did he die?",
        "type": "all",
        "reference": "2C 5:15",
        "answer": "all"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:1, if what were dissolved?",
        "type": "our earthly house of this tabernacle",
        "reference": "2C 5:1",
        "answer": "our earthly house of this tabernacle"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 5 which uses the word: bad",
        "type": "For we must all appear before the judgment seat of Christ; that every one may receive the things done in his body, according to that he hath done, whether it be good or bad.",
        "reference": "2C 5:10",
        "answer": "For we must all appear before the judgment seat of Christ; that every one may receive the things done in his body, according to that he hath done, whether it be good or bad."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:11, in what two ways are we made manifest?",
        "type": "unto God; and I trust also are made manifest in your consciences",
        "reference": "2C 5:11",
        "answer": "unto God; and I trust also are made manifest in your consciences"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:9, how may we be accepted of him?",
        "type": "whether present or absent",
        "reference": "2C 5:9",
        "answer": "whether present or absent"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:15, who hath no part with an infidel?",
        "type": "he that believeth",
        "reference": "2C 6:15",
        "answer": "he that believeth"
    },
    {
        "question": "How be not unequally yoked in 2 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "(together) with unbelievers",
        "reference": "2C 6:14",
        "answer": "(together) with unbelievers"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:18, how hath God reconciled us to himself?",
        "type": "by Jesus Christ",
        "reference": "2C 5:18",
        "answer": "by Jesus Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "As what approving ourselves in 2 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "the ministers of God",
        "reference": "2C 6:4",
        "answer": "the ministers of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:19, what did God not impute unto them?",
        "type": "their trespasses",
        "reference": "2C 5:19",
        "answer": "their trespasses"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:14, who were dead?",
        "type": "all",
        "reference": "2C 5:14",
        "answer": "all"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:11, what is enlarged?",
        "type": "our heart",
        "reference": "2C 6:11",
        "answer": "our heart"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:7, where is the armour of righteousness?",
        "type": "on the right hand and on the left",
        "reference": "2C 6:7",
        "answer": "on the right hand and on the left"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whom may ye have somewhat to answer in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "them which glory in appearance (and not in heart)",
        "reference": "2C 5:12",
        "answer": "them which glory in appearance (and not in heart)"
    },
    {
        "question": "What in 2 Corinthians 6 is open unto you?",
        "type": "our mouth",
        "reference": "2C 6:11",
        "answer": "our mouth"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:5, what hath God given us?",
        "type": "the earnest of the Spirit",
        "reference": "2C 5:5",
        "answer": "the earnest of the Spirit"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Almighty in 2 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "the Lord",
        "reference": "2C 6:18",
        "answer": "the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:12, what do we give you occasion to do?",
        "type": "to glory on our behalf",
        "reference": "2C 5:12",
        "answer": "to glory on our behalf"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:8, what are two reports?",
        "type": "evil report and good report",
        "reference": "2C 6:8",
        "answer": "evil report and good report"
    },
    {
        "question": "When have I succoured thee in 2 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "in the day of salvation",
        "reference": "2C 6:2",
        "answer": "in the day of salvation"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:18, what will the Lord be?",
        "type": "a Father unto you",
        "reference": "2C 6:18",
        "answer": "a Father unto you"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:7, of whom is the power?",
        "type": "of God",
        "reference": "2C 6:7",
        "answer": "of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "What touch not in 2 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "the unclean thing",
        "reference": "2C 6:17",
        "answer": "the unclean thing"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:13, what is for your cause?",
        "type": "(it) whether we be sober",
        "reference": "2C 5:13",
        "answer": "(it) whether we be sober"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:16, who will walk in them?",
        "type": "(I) God",
        "reference": "2C 6:16",
        "answer": "(I) God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where are ye straitened in 2 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "in your own bowels",
        "reference": "2C 6:12",
        "answer": "in your own bowels"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: By the word of truth, by the power of God, by the armour of righteousness on the right hand and on the left,",
        "type": "2 Corinthians 6:7",
        "reference": "2C 6:7",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 6:7"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:6, when are we absent from the Lord?",
        "type": "whilst we are at home in the body",
        "reference": "2C 5:6",
        "answer": "whilst we are at home in the body"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Christ's stead, what do we pray you in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "be ye reconciled to God",
        "reference": "2C 5:20",
        "answer": "be ye reconciled to God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:17, what are become new?",
        "type": "all things",
        "reference": "2C 5:17",
        "answer": "all things"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 5 which uses the word: creature",
        "type": "Therefore if any man be in Christ, he is a new creature: old things are passed away; behold, all things are become new.",
        "reference": "2C 5:17",
        "answer": "Therefore if any man be in Christ, he is a new creature: old things are passed away; behold, all things are become new."
    },
    {
        "question": "Whose ambassadors are we in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "Christ's",
        "reference": "2C 5:20",
        "answer": "Christ's"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 6 which uses the word: unrighteousness",
        "type": "Be ye not unequally yoked together with unbelievers: for what fellowship hath righteousness with unrighteousness? and what communion hath light with darkness?",
        "reference": "2C 6:14",
        "answer": "Be ye not unequally yoked together with unbelievers: for what fellowship hath righteousness with unrighteousness? and what communion hath light with darkness?"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:10, what are we making many?",
        "type": "rich",
        "reference": "2C 6:10",
        "answer": "rich"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:16, whom have we known after the flesh?",
        "type": "Christ",
        "reference": "2C 5:16",
        "answer": "Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:14, which two's fellowship is questioned?",
        "type": "righteousness (with) unrighteousness",
        "reference": "2C 6:14",
        "answer": "righteousness (with) unrighteousness"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:17, what be ye?",
        "type": "separate",
        "reference": "2C 6:17",
        "answer": "separate"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 5:20.",
        "type": "Now then we are ambassadors for Christ, as though God did beseech you by us: we pray you in Christ's stead, be ye reconciled to God.",
        "reference": "2C 5:20",
        "answer": "Now then we are ambassadors for Christ, as though God did beseech you by us: we pray you in Christ's stead, be ye reconciled to God."
    },
    {
        "question": "What might mortality be in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "swallowed up of life.",
        "reference": "2C 5:4",
        "answer": "swallowed up of life."
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"And what agreement hath the temple of God with idols? for ye are the temple of the living God.\"",
        "type": "as God hath said, I will dwell in them, and walk in them; and I will be their God, and they shall be my people",
        "reference": "2C 6:16",
        "answer": "as God hath said, I will dwell in them, and walk in them; and I will be their God, and they shall be my people"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:10, what may everyone receive?",
        "type": "the things done in his body (according to that he hath done, whether it be good or bad)",
        "reference": "2C 5:10",
        "answer": "the things done in his body (according to that he hath done, whether it be good or bad)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:10, what are we possessing?",
        "type": "all things",
        "reference": "2C 6:10",
        "answer": "all things"
    }
]